<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<projects>
  <entry>
    <title>Amazon-clone</title>
    <description>
Display a list of products with their images, titles, prices, and ratings.
Allow users to browse and search for products. 
Show detailed information about a specific product, including description, reviews. 
Enable users to add products to a shopping cart, view the cart contents, adjust quantities, and remove items. 
Calculate and display the total price of the items in the cart. Implement a search feature that allows users to search for products by keywords.
Ensure that the application is responsive and works well on different devices and screen sizes, including desktops, tablets
Tech Stack Used: React, Tailwind CSS, Redux, Axios, Swiper.
Contribution:  Contribute to the development of new features for the Amazon clone. This can include implementing
     functionalities like product search, adding items to the cart, managing the cart.
</description>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Fitness App</title>
    <description>
User can choose exercise categories and speciﬁc muscle Group.
User can browse more than one thousand exercises with practical examples.
With the functionality to choose exercises with practical examples, pagination, exercises details, pull related videos from youtube, display similar exercise and much more.
Tech Stack Used: React, Material UI.
Contribution: This is React project where user can search the content related to Fitness/Exercises. 
</description>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>IOT based Automatic Colour Sorting Machine. | Final Year Project</title>
    <description>
Colour sorting machine is made of RPI, camera module, RPI monitor, Servo motor, Detector disk and ﬂapper.
Colour sorting machine sort the object accordingly to the colour and shape and put in the respective container and update  data on web app.
Web app is used to connect, reset, count data like sorting and counting of objects.
Fetch live data in app using Mqtt(Mosquitto telemetry transport).
Manual date and time update so it will gives notiﬁcations 2-3 prior before a month.
Designed UI is Mobile responsive. 
Whenever app starts freshly it will always back the last updated data on the cloud.
</description>
  </entry>
  
</projects>